

### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am really motivated to continually improve my abilities and advancement professionally. I am confident in my abilities, which I have developed over the last 2 years. During this period, I've created numerous websites using Word Press and Shopify.

### **CONTACT ME**



H# 322, ST#3A, Singum Town, Khanapull Islamabad

Phone 0314-5506866

Email hamadraja550@gmail.com

ា Linkedin Hammad Irfan Rathore

### **SKILLS**

- Exceptional communication and networking skills Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently
- ✓ The ability to work under pressure and multi-task
- The ability to follow instructions and deliver quality results

### **LANGUAGE**

Urdu

Punjabi

**English** 

# HAMMAD IRFAN RATHORE

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Build a WooCommerce website.
- wpbakery, Divi & Beaver Builder.
- WordPress Plugins Development.
- WordPress Theme Development.
- Custom Post Type and Advance Custom Shopify Store setups, Apps Integrations.
- WordPress Hooks Action and Filter
- Front-end Development (HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Bootstrap3,4, javascript, jQuery).
- Back-end Development (MySQL, PHP).
- Google Analytics Configuration on Website.
- Constantly updated the Changes with Trends.  $_ullet$  Web Data Extraction Through Web Scraping

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **Hybrid Mediaworks** March 2024 - Continue

Markhorist Pvt

NOV 2023 - March 2024

**Global Advertising** 

### **Completed Projects**

Maintaining and updates projects

# **Completed Projects**

iminka.com

NOV 2021 - NOV 2023

# **Completed Projects**

- nooraahmad.com
- quantocoin.io

• reachoutdubai.com

blueoasis.com fossilpk.com

# **Wurfel IT Branding IT**

**IAN 2021- NOV 2021** 

### **Completed Projects**

- silvermark.pk
- piccadillyhomes.com
- osmium.pk/construction amaarlodges.com/project
- aristasolar.com
- elt.com.pk

### **Freelancing Projects**

### **Completed Projects**

- ornatesystems.com
  prmassociates.pk
- theheraldprime.pk securedeals.ae
- mksproperty.ie
- thrivenewswire.com
- nemtwise.com

### **EDUCATION**

## AJK Board of Intermediate & Secondary Education, Mirpur

Matric

# **Punjab Skills Development programme**

- 1.Web designing and development
- 2. Fiber optic
- 3.Basic computer course

# Digiskills.pk

- 1. Wordpress Development
- 2.Freelancing
- 3.E-commorce management programme